http://www.accessgroup.org/terms-use

Terms of Use
AccessLex Institute d/b/a Access Group and Access Group Education Lending® (“Access Group”), a non-profit corporation, maintains this website, www.accessgroup.org, to provide individuals who have Access Group student loans, and Access Group loan investors, with general information about Access Group, with information on third party loan servicing and collections, and with investor reporting information (the “Site”).  Please read the following terms and conditions carefully.  By using the Site, you agree to be subject to these terms and conditions, including any terms and conditions that may be modified from time to time without notice, and our Privacy Policy, and you agree that you will not use the Site for any unlawful purpose. These terms and conditions constitute the entire agreement between Access Group and you concerning your use of the Site.
Restrictions on Use
All contents of the Site, including the design, “look and feel,” layout, graphics, images, logos, icons, software, text or video are the property of Access Group and are protected by the United States and international copyright and trademark laws.  Subject to the terms and conditions outlined below, you may download, reprint or reproduce the information and materials contained in the Site solely for personal or other non-commercial purposes so long as you do not modify the information and you keep intact any copyright notices as they appear in these materials.  No portion of the information or materials contained in the Site may be downloaded, reprinted, republished, modified or distributed for commercial purposes without the express written permission of Access Group.
You agree that you will not use any robot, spider, scraper or any other automatic or computer-generated device or manual process to monitor or copy the Site pages or content contained herein without Access Group’s express written permission.  You further agree that you will not use any device, software or routine to interfere or attempt to interfere with the proper working of the Site or any transaction being conducted on the Site.
Security
In using the services on the Site, you may be asked to provide personal information about yourself.  Access Group’s collection, use and disclosure of personal information are governed by our Privacy Policy.
If you register on the Site, you will be requested to create a password and username.  You are solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account, including the security of your password.  You agree that Access Group shall not be liable for any loss that you may suffer as a result of any use of your password by a third party, whether authorized or unauthorized.
You agree to notify us, via e-mail at support@accessgroup.org, promptly in the event of any unauthorized use of your password and/or account and any breach of security relating to your use of the Site.
Copyright and Trademark Notice
Access Advisor, Access Advisor Administrator, Access Alert, Access Assist, Access Group, Access Insight, Business Access, Comprehensive Access, Dental Access, Graduate Access, Health Access, Informed Access, “Know the Options, Get the Answers,” Law Access, “Leading the Conversation,” Medical Access, Need Access, No Worries, Optimum Access, Sponsored Access, The Access Group, Welcome Access, Wiseborrower, 844-WISEPAY, the mortar board logo and the “Access Group” logos are trademarks, service marks and logos of Access Group.  Access Group reserves the right to amend this list of trademarks, service marks and logos at any time.  All other trademarks, service marks and logos used in the Site are the trademarks, service marks or logos of their respective owners.  You may not use, copy, display, distribute, modify or reproduce any of the copyrighted materials or trademarks contained in the Site, except as authorized herein.
Disclaimer, Limitation of Liability and Indemnification
BY USING THE SITE, YOU ASSUME TOTAL RESPONSIBILITY AND RISK FOR YOUR USE OF THE SITE, SITE-RELATED SERVICES AND ANY HYPERLINKS.  THE SITE AND ALL CONTENT AND INFORMATION CONTAINED HEREIN ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” WITH NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. ACCESS GROUP IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR AND EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY THIRD PARTY WEBSITES LINKED ON THIS SITE, WHICH ARE LINKED SOLELY AS A CONVENIENCE FOR YOU, AND WHICH ARE SUBJECT TO THE PRIVACY POLICY AND TERMS OF USE OF THE APPLICABLE THIRD PARTY. ACCESS GROUP IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE DELETION OF OR FAILURE TO STORE ANY DATA OR OTHER INFORMATION PROVIDED BY YOU ON THE SITE.  ACCESS GROUP MAKES NO WARRANTY THAT THE SERVICE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR FREE, NOR DOES IT MAKE ANY WARRANTY THAT THE SERVICE WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS OR AS TO THE RESULTS THAT MAY BE OBTAINED FROM USE OF THE SERVICE.  YOUR NEEDS AND REQUIREMENTS MAY BE DIFFERENT DEPENDING ON YOUR PARTICULAR CIRCUMSTANCES AND ACCESS GROUP DOES NOT GUARANTEE THE APPLICABILITY OR ACCURACY OF INFORMATION PROVIDED ON THE SITE TO YOUR PARTICULAR CIRCUMSTANCES.  THE INFORMATION AND TOOLS MADE AVAILABLE ON THE SITE ARE NOT INTENDED TO PROVIDE FINANCIAL OR INVESTMENT ADVICE. IT IS RECOMMENDED THAT YOU SEEK THE ADVICE OF A FINANCIAL ADVISOR OR ATTORNEY WHO CAN REVIEW YOUR PARTICULAR CIRCUMSTANCES AND REQUIREMENTS BEFORE YOU IMPLEMENT ANY FINANCIAL STRATEGY.
ACCESS GROUP AND ITS AFFILIATES SHALL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, PUNITIVE OR OTHER DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING IN ANY WAY TO THE SITE, SITE-RELATED SERVICES, CONTENT OR INFORMATION CONTAINED WITHIN THE SITE AND/OR ANY HYPERLINKS WHETHER BASED IN CONTRACT, TORT, NEGLIGENCE, STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE.  YOUR SOLE REMEDY FOR DISSATISFACTION WITH THE SITE, SITE-RELATED SERVICES, CONTENT OR INFORMATION CONTAINED WITHIN THE SITE AND/OR HYPERLINKS IS TO STOP USING THE SITE AND/OR THE SERVICES, CONTENT OR INFORMATION.
YOU AGREE TO INDEMNIFY, DEFEND AND HOLD HARMLESS ACCESS GROUP, ITS DIRECTORS, OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES AND AGENTS FROM AND AGAINST ALL LOSSES, EXPENSES, DAMAGES AND COSTS, INCLUDING REASONABLE ATTORNEYS’ FEES, ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO USE OF THE SITE BY YOU OR ANY OTHER PERSON ACCESSING THE SITE USING YOUR NAME AND/OR PASSWORD.
Although Access Group attempts to ensure the integrity and accurateness of the Site, it makes no guarantees as to the accuracy of any of the contents or information, that your access to the Site will be uninterrupted or that content accessed from the Site or that of any third party sites accessed through a hyperlink is free of viruses, worms, Trojan Horses or other code with destructive properties.
Third Party Links
The Site contains links to third party websites as a convenience to provide you with additional information and functionality.  By offering hyperlinks to third party websites, Access Group does not represent or imply that there is any relationship between it and any third party or that it is endorsing those third parties or their products or services and is not responsible for the privacy policies or terms of use of any such third parties. Additionally, the third party sites linked on this Site may contain privacy policies and/or terms of use specifically for those third-party websites, which may differ from the policies and terms set forth on this Site. If you are visiting a third party site, please be sure to review that Site's privacy policy and terms of use. Access Group expressly disclaims any responsibility for the contents of any third party site.
Choice of Law and Venue
These terms and conditions are entered into in the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania and shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, exclusive of its choice of law rules.  By using the Site, you agree to submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the state and federal courts in Chester County, Pennsylvania and waive any jurisdictional, venue or inconvenient forum objections to such courts.  In any action to enforce these terms and conditions, the prevailing party will be entitled to costs and attorneys’ fees.  In the event that any of these terms and conditions are held by a court or other tribunal of competent jurisdiction to be unenforceable, such provisions shall be limited or eliminated to the extent necessary so that these terms and conditions shall otherwise remain in full force and effect.
Accessibility
If you have difficulty accessing any content on this website, we encourage you to reach out to us directly so that we can improve our efforts to accomodate our audience and otherwise provide you with the resources and information that you may be seeking.
Rev. November 2018
